RG 142, General Federation of Women's Clubs of Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Administrative Files, 1896-2012
  - T001355
    - Files, 1965 March 8-1968 May 9; 4 folders; Contains documents from the administrations of Mrs. John B. Fahey, Mrs. James G. Osmond, and Mrs. William F. Hayes. Includes budgets, correspondence, minutes, programs, and reports. (Box 20)
    - President's council, 1966 May 3-1974 March 14; 1 binder (Box 21)
    - Files, 1962 June 6-1968 March 5; 2 folders; Includes budgets, correspondence, minutes, programs, and reports. (Box 21)
    - Public affairs department, undated; 1 binder (Box 21)
    - Mrs. James G. Osmond, president, 1966 June 23-1968 April 27; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Mrs. William Hayes, president, 1968 June 3-1970 March 19; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Majorcan carnival, correspondence and details, 1971 November 4-1972 February 14; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Documents, 1972 June 8-1974 May 9; 3 folders; Includes budgets, correspondence, minutes, programs, and reports. (Box 23)
    - Citation for achievement in membership, 1974 May 29; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Certificate of appreciation, 1971 September 13 (Box 24)
    - President's messages, 1972 September 13-1974 February (Box 24)
    - Executive board, 1972 June 22-1974 February 28 (Box 24)
    - Executive committee, 1972 May 4-1974 May 6 (Box 24)
    - Guestbook, 1967 September 19-1971 November 3; 1 volume (Box 24)
    - Pointers for Participation, 1974-1976 (Box 25)
    - Laurina G. Pettis, president, 1974 May 7-1976 May 6; 1 binder (Box 25)
    - Auditors reports, 1975 May 2-1978 March 31 (Box 26)
    - Energy conservation materials, 1976 November-1978 March 25 (Box 26)
    - Calls to meetings, 1976 October 9-1977 April 5 (Box 26)
    - Home energy check, 1976-1978 April 5 (Box 26)
    - Junior Bulletins, 1976 September-1978 June (Box 26)
    - Pointers for Participation, 1976-1978 June (Box 26)
    - Reports, 1976-1978 June (Box 26)
    - Reports, 1977 February 21-1977 June 25 (Box 26)
    - Calls to meetings, 1977 October 4-1978 May 6 (Box 26)
    - State federation business, 1976-1978 May 6 (Box 26)
    - Documents, 1976 June 14-1978 May 25; 2 folders; Includes calls to meetings, correspondence, programs, and resolutions. (Box 27)
    - Executive board minutes, 1976 June 29-1978 March 21 (Box 27)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1976 May 6-1978 May 3 (Box 27)
    - Juniors and juniorettes, 1976-1978 (Box 27)
    - Projects, 1976-1978 (Box 27)
    - Reports, 1976-1978; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1976 April 1-1978 April 1 (Box 27)
    - Conferences and conventions, 1978 October 24-1980 May 8; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Documents, 1978 August 2-1980 April 16; 2 folders; Includes calls to meetings, programs, and official statement from Governor Ella Grasso, designating April 20-26, 1980, as Women's Clubs Week. (Box 28)
    - Executive board minutes, 1978 June 20-1980 March 11 (Box 28)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1978 June 20-1980 March 11 (Box 28)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1978 May-1980 May 1 (Box 28)
    - Documents, 1978 May-1980 May 20; Includes correspondence, reports, and speeches. (Box 29)
    - Insurance, 1979 October 18-1980 January 6 (Box 29)
    - Juniors, 1978 July 6-1979 October (Box 29)
    - Pilot program, smoking awareness, 1979 October 30-1979 December 8 (Box 29)
    - Pointers for Participation, 1978-1980 (Box 29)
    - Pointers for Participation, Supplement, 1979 (Box 29)
    - Project share, 1978 April 26-1978 November 7 (Box 29)
    - Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 29)
    - Certificates of appreciation, 1981 April 29-1981 October 13 (Box 30)
    - Documents, 1978 May-1980 May 20; Includes board of directors, newsletter, pamphlets, and resolutions. (Box 30)
    - Pointers for Participation, 1980-1982 (Box 30)
    - Pointers for Participation, supplement, 1981-1982 (Box 30)
    - Projects, 1980-1982; 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Reports and histories, 1980-1982 (Box 30)
    - Reports of departments, 1980-1982; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Documents, 1980 May 16-1982 February 16; 1 binder; Calls to meetings, correspondence, newspaper clippings, programs, projects, and reports. (Box 32)
    - Certificates of Appreciation from Save the Children Federation, 1973 October 31; 1 certificate in glass frame (Box 33)
    - Certificates of Appreciation from the Republic of Korea, undated; 1 certificate in glass frame (Box 33)
  - 1986-034
    - Minutes, 1955 May 5-1957 May 9; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Minutes, 1957 June 20-1960 May 4; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Minutes, 1960 June 8-1962 May 3 (Box 1)
    - Minutes, 1962 May 3-1964 May 7; 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1962 May 4-1966 May 5 (Box 1)
    - Attendance, 1964 May 7-1965 September 30 (Box 1)
    - Conventions and conferences, 1964 November 4-1966 May 5 (Box 1)
    - Executive board minutes, 1964 June 18-1966 March 24 (Box 1)
    - Historian, 1958; Includes three statewide federation histories, covering 1954-1958. (Box 2)
    - Health in schools, 1956 June-1963 January 8 (Box 2)
    - Annual reports, 1959 May 21-1964 May 6 (Box 2)
    - Credential reports, 1960 May 4-1963 May 9 (Box 2)
    - Calls and programs, 1960 November 3-1964 June 18 (Box 2)
    - Bylaws, 1962 July 7-1962 November 7 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1962 April 19-1963 May 2 (Box 2)
    - Hartford Junior Woman's Club History 1933-1963 (Box 2)
    - Reports given at 66th annual convention, 1963 May 7-1963 May 9 (Box 2)
    - Attendance, 1966 May 5-1968 March 28 (Box 2)
    - Executive board minutes, 1966 June 23-1968 March 13 (Box 2)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1966 May 5-1968 May 7 (Box 2)
    - Conferences and conventions, 1966 November 2-1968 May 9; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Resolutions, 1964 September 8-1965 November (Box 3)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1964 May 5-1966 May 3 (Box 3)
    - Fall conferences, 1972 October 25-1973 October 31 (Box 3)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1972 May 4-1973 May 31 (Box 3)
    - Attendance, 1972 May 4-1974 February 28 (Box 3)
    - Board addresses, 1972-1974 (Box 3)
    - Calls to meetings, 1973 May 1-1974 February 23 (Box 3)
    - Conventions, 1972 May 1-1974 May 9; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Executive board minutes, 1972 June 22-1974 February 28 (Box 3)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1972 May 4-1974 May 8 (Box 3)
    - Officers and dates, 1972-1974 (Box 3)
    - Membership study, 1973 May 8-1974 March 19 (Box 3)
    - Conventions and conferences, 1974 March-1976 October 26 (Box 3)
    - District meetings, 1974 August 19-1976 October 4 (Box 3)
    - Public affairs, Connecticut juniors, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1966 April 4-1968 April 26 (Box 4)
    - Attendance, 1968 July 17-1970 March 7 (Box 4)
    - Executive board minutes, 1968 August 8-1970 March 7 (Box 4)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1968 June 17-1970 March 7 (Box 4)
    - Fall conferences and conventions, 1968 November 6-1970 May 6 (Box 4)
    - Attendance, 1970 May 7-1972 March 2 (Box 4)
    - Conferences and conventions, 1970 November 4-1972 May 4 (Box 4)
    - Executive board minutes, 1970 June 17-1972 March 7 (Box 4)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1970 May 7-1972 March 2 (Box 4)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1970 May 6-1972 May 1 (Box 4)
    - Focus newsletters, 1976 September-1978 June (Box 4)
    - Meetings and conferences, 1974 September 25-1976 April 24 (Box 5)
    - Club business, 1974 May 24-1977 June (Box 5)
    - Club activities, 1974 November 12-1980 June 29 (Box 5)
    - Executive board minutes, 1976 June 29-1978 March 21 (Box 5)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1976 May 6-1978 May 3 (Box 5)
    - Conventions and conferences, 1977 May 3-1977 May 5 (Box 5)
    - Conventions and conferences, 1978 May 4-1979 June 8 (Box 5)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1976 May 1-1978 April 1 (Box 5)
  - 1987-029
    - Ursula, miscellaneous, 1976 June-1978; Includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, and reports. (Box 1)
    - State awards, 1984 March 26-1986 April 26 (Box 1)
    - Calls, 1984 May 23-1986 March 26 (Box 1)
    - Cancer, 1979 September 20-1985 January 29 (Box 1)
    - Community improvement program, 1982 October-1985 October 24 (Box 1)
    - Cookbook, 1985 March 12-1986 November 14 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut public expenditure council, 1984 April 27-1986 May 15 (Box 1)
    - Conventions, 1985 March 25-1986 May 8 (Box 1)
    - Letters and correspondence, 1984 November 29-1986 July 10 (Box 1)
    - Suffield Woman's Club, 1985 Febuary 1-1985 May 23 (Box 1)
    - Departments, 1983 October 3-1985 November 26 (Box 1)
    - Districts, 1984 October 23-1985 October 22 (Box 1)
    - Fall conference, 1984 October 23-1985 October 22 (Box 1)
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1984 June 15-1986 June 22; Contains information on the state federation's name change from the Connecticut State Federation of Women's Clubs, Inc., to the General Federation of Women's Clubs of Connecticut, Inc. (Box 1)
    - Governor's council volunteers, 1982 May 25-1986 June 5 (Box 1)
    - Greenwoods, 1985 August 5-1986 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Laurel Girls' State, 1985 June 23-1986 June 28 (Box 1)
    - Crusaders and Criminals book, 1985 September 11-1986 October 16 (Box 1)
    - Laurel Music Camp, 1985 June 28-1986 June 27 (Box 1)
    - Law related education, 1986 July 15-1986 December 23 (Box 1)
    - Library, 1926 June 29-1986 March 12 (Box 1)
    - New England conference, 1985 September 24-1985 October 6 (Box 1)
    - Nominating committee, 1985 May 7-1986 January 1 (Box 1)
    - Lafontaine, executive committee meetings, 1986 May 8-1988 May 2 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, executive board meetings, 1986 June 20-1988 March 15 (Box 2)
    - Fall conference, Lafontaine, 1986 October 21-1987 October 20 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, district spring meetings, 1987 April 8-1988 April 16 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, state convention, 1987 May 5-1988 May 5 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, New England conference, Mystic, Connecticut, 1986 September 22-1987 September 24 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine Focus, 1986 September-1988 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, yearbook, 1986-1988 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, Ferrol Miller Bleakley Scholarship, 1986 May 14-1987 May 9 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, Dorothy E. Schoelzel Memorial Scholarship, 1987 July 10-1988 June 1 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, report nominating committee, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, awards, 1986 June 27-1988 April 19 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, Jefferson Awards, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, Special Olympics, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, Hugh O'Brian Youth Foundation, 1987 June 3-1988 May 1 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Coalition for Literacy, Lafontaine, 1986 August 16-1987 March (Box 2)
    - State project, remove intoxicated drivers, 1986 December 24-1989 June 23 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, workshops, 1986 September 29-1988 February 2 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, bylaw amendments, 1986 October 21-1988 May 5 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, letters, 1986 November 17-1988 June 30 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, resolutions, 1987 May-1988 May (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, honorary president Gladys Johnson's book, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Lafontaine, president's installation, reports, letters, 1986 May 7-1988 June (Box 2)
    - Correspondence-Allyn, Edward A., 1910 May 14-1910 December 13 (Box 2)
    - Officers reports, 1984 June 1-1986 March 27 (Box 2)
    - Phipps, 1985 April 25-1986 (Box 2)
    - Profile, letterhead, printing, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
    - Pointers supplement, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Special Olympics, 1985 July 8-1986 June 15 (Box 2)
    - Red book, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
    - Resolutions, 1962 November 7-1976 (Box 2)
    - Resolutions, 1986 December 1 (Box 2)
    - State Project, Paul and Lisa, 1985 October 17-1986 November 9 (Box 2)
    - Trans national, 1985 May 6-1986 (Box 2)
    - Minutes and treasurer's reports, 1984 June 22-1986 June 1 (Box 2)
    - Officers reports, 1984 June 1-1986 March 27 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Women cookbook, undated (Box 2)
  - 1992-089
    - Documents, 1982 June 1-1984 June 1; 4 folders; Includes calls to meetings, certificates of appreciation, financial statements, minutes, proclamations, programs, and reports. (Box 1)
  - 1996-018
    - Financial accounts, 1897-1993; 9 volumes; Includes records of daily receipts, treasurer's annual reports, the Phipps scholarship fund, and the endowment fund for president's expenses. (Box 1)
    - Documents, 1985 March 27-1990 February 5; 1 folder; Includes Clubwoman's Song, correspondence, and reporting forms. (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1986 September 26-1990 May 9 (Box 2)
    - Documents, 1987 April 22-1990 May 5; 1 folder; Includes calls to meetings, guidelines, petitions, and programs. (Box 2)
    - Executive committee calls, 1988 August 16-1989 December 2 (Box 2)
    - New England conference, 1988 September 19-1989 September 21 (Box 2)
    - Workshops, fall conference, 1988 October -1989 November 9 (Box 2)
    - Agendas, 1988 May 6-1990 March 15 (Box 2)
    - Annual conventions, fall conferences, 1988 October 18-1990 May 5 (Box 2)
    - Convention, 1988 May 3-1990 May 5 (Box 2)
    - Convention committee meetings, 1988 May 3-1990 January 27 (Box 2)
    - District meetings, 1988 June 7-1990 April 21 (Box 2)
    - Executive board calls, 1988 July 9-1990 March 15 (Box 2)
    - Executive board minutes, 1988 July 9-1990 March 15 (Box 2)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1988 May 5-1990 May 2 (Box 2)
    - FIDELCO Guide Dog Foundation and centennial, 1988-1990 April 28 (Box 2)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1988 June 1-1990 April 1 (Box 2)
    - Membership, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1990 May 16-1991 June 25 (Box 3)
    - Fall conference, 1990 October 23-1991 October 17 (Box 3)
    - Board meeting calls, 1990 July 20-1991 June 20 (Box 3)
    - Convention, 1990 April-1992 February 8 (Box 3)
    - Executive board minutes, 1990 July 21-1992 March 21 (Box 3)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1990 May 5-1992 May 6 (Box 3)
    - Fall conference and convention minutes, 1990 September 23-1992 May 9 (Box 3)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1990 May 31-1992 May 1 (Box 3)
    - Convention committee minutes, 1991 January 19-1992 May 6 (Box 3)
    - Fall conference, 1992 October 20-1993 October 26 (Box 3)
    - Executive board minutes, 1992 June 19-1994 March 19 (Box 3)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1992 May 9-1994 May 4 (Box 3)
    - Documents, 1992 September 1-1994 May 7; 1 folder; Includes calendars, news clippings, projects, and programs. (Box 3)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1992 June 1-1994 June 1 (Box 3)
    - Annual convention, 1993 May 14-1994 May 7 (Box 3)
  - 2001-028
    - Minutes, 1994 May 6-1995 May 6; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Minutes, 1995 October 24-1996 May 10; 1 volume (Box 1)
  - 2002-022
    - Minutes, 1992 May 9-1994 May 7; 2 volumes (Box 1 envelope)
  - 2002-085
    - Records, 1990 October 11-1995 March 25; 1 folder; Includes calls to meetings, correspondence, list of awards, minutes, newsletters, and reports. (Box 1)
    - Documents, 1998 June 18-2000 May 7; 2 volumes; Includes correspondence, list of awards and best programs, minutes, and reports. (Box 1)
  - 2003-018
    - Year Book, 2000-2002; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - The Next Place, 2002; 1 volume; The General Federation of Women's Clubs of Connecticut donated this book to libraries, schools, and to the families of victims of the September 11, 2001 terrorist attacks on the United States. The federation's donations of this book are described on page 755 of the third volume of documents in Box 1. (Box 1)
    - Documents, 1998 June 18-2000 May 7; 3 volumes; Includes calls to meetings, correspondence, minutes, publications, publicity, reports, resolutions, and state projects. (Box 1)
  - 2005-007
    - Year Book, 2000-2004; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Canine Search and Rescue, 2004; Includes a book, Emma and the Night Dogs, about canine search and rescue, as well as testimony from Jean Brown, the federation's state president, in support of protection for search and rescue volunteers. (Box 1)
    - Connecticut for safe roads, undated (Box 1)
    - Financial statements, 2002 May 31-2003 May 31 (Box 1)
    - Documents, 2000 June 18-2004 May 7; 3 volumes; Includes bylaws changes, calls to meetings, correspondence, minutes, publications, reports, resolutions, and state projects. (Box 1)
    - Centennial gala, 1998 April 23; 1 volume; Includes histories and copies of correspondence, newspaper clippings, and photographs. (Box 1)
  - 2013-024
    - Lafontaine, VIP Award list, 1988-2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut Food Bank Project, 2010 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 501(c)3 status, 2010 July (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - State officers, 2010 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Certificates of recognition, 2010 October 16-2011 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, cyberbullying, 2010 October 16-2011 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - New England conferences, 2010 September 24-2011 September 25 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Administration report, 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - American mural project, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Calls to meetings, 2010 July 24-2012 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Club manual, 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Colors of Friendship, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, general, 2010 September 24-2012 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, thank-you's, 2010 May 19-2012 June 1; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
    - Minutes, 2010 May 15-2012 May 18; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
    - Vets OASIS grand opening, 2010-2012 March 21; Digital video disc of Vets OASIS television show separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Senior high school art festival, 2011 March 18 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - State president's annual report, 2011 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - District meetings, programs, 2011 April 7-2012 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Domestic violence, 2011 September-2012 February (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 2011-2012 April (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Public relations committee handout, 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Proposed slate of officers, 2012 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 2016-009
    - Convention planning meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1 compact disc containing 37 Microsoft Word documents has been removed from folder to Series 9. Removable Media. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - Executive committee minutes, 2008 May 31-2009 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Executive board minutes, 2008 Septmeber 27-2010 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Conventions / orientations, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Vets OASIS, circa 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Vets OASIS, Channel 23, Danbury, circa 2010, 1 digital video disc, has been removed from folder to Series 8. Video. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - American Mural Project, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      American Mural Project, Winsted, 2009, 1 digital video disc, has been removed from folder to Series 8. Video. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - Board of directors meeting, Arlington, Virginia, 2008 September 4-7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Pointers, 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - District 1 meetings, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - District 2 meetings, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - District 3 meetings, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - District 4 meetings, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - District 5 meetings, 2007-2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - District 6 meetings, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - District 7 meetings, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Convention booklets and invites, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Award certificate, 2010-2012, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      The folder contains reports; list of members who participated in meetings; and The Insider the Farmington Valley Woman's Club newsletter edition 61.
    - Financial report of districts, 2008 June-2009 May (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Red book, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Series 2. Publications, 1898-1972
  - T001355
    - Histories, 1898-1982 April (Box 1)
    - The Connecticut Club Courier, 1933-1945; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Golden Jubilee, 1941 May (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Clubwoman, 1961 February-1963 October (Box 1)
    - Junior Bulletin, 1978 June-1979 March (Box 1)
    - Focus, 1978 October-1982 May; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Best program and best ways and means lists, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - Directory, 1980-1982 (Box 2)
    - District newsletters, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Book donated to national federation of woman's clubs, 2008 (Box 2)
    - Club yearbooks and state directories, 1900-1982 May; 2 volumes and 86 booklets (Box 3)
- Series 3. Press Books and Scrapbooks, 1897-1967
  - T001355
    - Scrapbook, 1897 April 20-1901 November 22; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1935 May 22-1941 May 24; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Notices of state meetings and county meetings, 1946 April 6-1946 May 23; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Press book contest records, 1943-1957 April; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Press book, 1946 June 26-1947 May 15; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Press book, 1947 August 17-1949 May 22; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Press book, 1950 August 28-1951 May 23; 1 volume (Box 3)
    - Press book, 1951 June 3-1952 June 21; 1 volume (Box 4)
    - Press book contest records, 1957 October 1-1964 April 29; 1 volume (Box 4)
    - Mrs. John Arthur Bjerkoe, president, 1955 April 30-1957 May 11; 2 volumes; Contains press clippings and programs. (Box 5)
  - 2009-008
    - Scrapbook, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1966-1967; 1 volume (Box 1)
- Series 4. Centennial, 1995-1998
  - T001355
    - Administration handbook, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Administration logos, 1996 July 17-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Administration Pointers, 1996 July 17-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alpha Home, 1996 September 24-1998 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Angels Doll Tea, 1995 March 25-1998 April 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Board of directors, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Centennial, 1997 March 26-1997 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Centennial correspondence, 1996 November 29-1997 April 28 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations/proclamations, 1996 October 18-1997 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut breast cancer coalition, 1996 October 1-1998 March 17 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Districts, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Doll Project, 1997 February 24-1998 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Fall conference, 1996 June 10-1997 October 27 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Focus, 1996 September-1998 March (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising, 1996 February 28-1997 October 9 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising tea, 1996 August 28-1996 November 19 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Convention, 1996 June 13-1998 June 15 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Seminars, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - History play, 1996 September 23-1997 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Hugh O'Brian Youth Leadership, 1997 March 23-1998 March 15 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Installation reception, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Internal correspondence, 1996 June 3-1997 May 14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Legislation day, 1996 June 28-1997 November 12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Libraries 2000, 1997 November 21-1998 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Membership, 1996 July 22-1998 January 17 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Membership, Greenwich, 1996 October 8-1998 February 19 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Membership scholarships, 1996 July 31-1998 May 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1995 July 7-1998 July 9 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - New England region, 1996 September 27-1998 April 21 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - New Orleans display, 1998 January 8-1998 June 13 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Photo highlights, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Pre-convention dinner, tour, display, 1996 July 16-1997 May 5 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Orientations, 1995 July 7-1997 June 28 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Pioneer woman, 1998 May 5 (Box 3, Folder 13)